<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<T3locallang>
	<meta type="array">
		<description>language labels for tt_news</description>
		<type>module</type>
		<csh_table></csh_table>
		<fileId>EXT:tt_news/locallang.xml</fileId>
		<labelContext type="array">
			<label index="pi_title"></label>
			<label index="pi_plus_wiz_description"></label>
		</labelContext>
	</meta>
	<data type="array">
		<languageKey index="default" type="array">
			<label index="pi_title">News</label>
			<label index="pi_plus_wiz_description">Versatile news system for TYPO3</label>
			<label index="cms_layout.mode">Displaying: %s</label>
			<label index="cms_layout.not_configured">Plugin is not configured!</label>
			
			<label index="updater.back">[&lt;- back]</label>
			<label index="updater.reload">[reload this page]</label>
			
			<label index="updater.lbl_searchOutdatedTempl">Search for outdated static TS templates</label>
			<label index="updater.msg_searchOutdatedTempl">Search for TypoScript templates which include one of the tt_news static templates (e.g. "CSS based tmpl") but with an outdated path:</label>
			<label index="updater.foundMsg_searchOutdatedTempl">Found ###COUNT### template records.</label>
			<label index="updater.question_searchOutdatedTempl">Should the updater update these records?</label>
			<label index="updater.questionInfo_searchOutdatedTempl">(If you click "DO IT" the updater script will update these template records with a fixed path)</label>
			
			<label index="updater.lbl_searchNonExistingHtml">Search for non existing HTML templates</label>
			<label index="updater.msg_searchNonExistingHtml">Search for tt_news content elements with a configured HTML template in flexforms which doesn't exist in your filesystem:</label>
			<label index="updater.foundMsg_searchNonExistingHtml">Found ###COUNT### content elements.</label>
			<label index="updater.question_searchNonExistingHtml">Should the updater clean this settings?</label>
			<label index="updater.questionInfo_searchNonExistingHtml">(If you click "DO IT" the updater script will search all tt_news plugin content-elements for configured template files. If there are template files configured which do not exist under the configured path (e.g. "EXT:tt_news/pi/tt_news_v2_template.html") the updater will clean this settings. Then tt_news uses the default template which is configured in typoScript.)</label>
	
	
			<label index="updater.lbl_searchMovedPidlist">Search "Startingpoint" ("pages") in FF</label>
			<label index="updater.msg_searchMovedPidlist">Search for tt_news content elements with a value for "Startingpoint" in flexforms (This field was moved to another sheet):</label>
			<label index="updater.foundMsg_searchMovedPidlist">Found ###COUNT### content elements.</label>
			<label index="updater.question_searchMovedPidlist">Should the updater fix this settings?</label>
			<label index="updater.questionInfo_searchMovedPidlist">(If you click "DO IT" the entry will be moved to the new flexform sheet)</label>		
			
			<label index="updater.lbl_searchMovedRecursive">Search "recursive" in FF</label>
			<label index="updater.msg_searchMovedRecursive">Search for tt_news content elements with a value for "recursive" in flexforms (This field was moved to another sheet):</label>
			<label index="updater.foundMsg_searchMovedRecursive">Found ###COUNT### content elements.</label>
			<label index="updater.question_searchMovedRecursive">Should the updater fix this settings?</label>
			<label index="updater.questionInfo_searchMovedRecursive">(If you click "DO IT" the entry will be moved to the new flexform sheet)</label>		
			
			
			<label index="updater.lbl_searchMovedNoPageBrowser">Search "no page Browser" in FF</label>
			<label index="updater.msg_searchMovedNoPageBrowser">Search for tt_news content elements with a value for "noPageBrowser" in flexforms (This field was moved to another sheet):</label>
			<label index="updater.foundMsg_searchMovedNoPageBrowser">Found ###COUNT### content elements.</label>
			<label index="updater.question_searchMovedNoPageBrowser">Should the updater fix this settings?</label>
			<label index="updater.questionInfo_searchMovedNoPageBrowser">(If you click "DO IT" the entry will be moved to the new flexform sheet)</label>		
			
			<label index="updater.lbl_searchMovedListLimit">Search "listLimit" in FF</label>
			<label index="updater.msg_searchMovedListLimit">Search for tt_news content elements with a value for "listLimit" in flexforms (This field was moved to another sheet):</label>
			<label index="updater.foundMsg_searchMovedListLimit">Found ###COUNT### content elements.</label>
			<label index="updater.question_searchMovedListLimit">Should the updater fix this settings?</label>
			<label index="updater.questionInfo_searchMovedListLimit">(If you click "DO IT" the entry will be moved to the new flexform sheet)</label>		
				
				
			<label index="updater.warningHeader">Important! Please Read!</label>
			<label index="updater.nothingtodo">Nothing to do</label>
			<label index="updater.actions">Actions:</label>
			<label index="updater.updateresults">Update results:</label>
			
			<label index="updater.warningMsg">The updater manipulates your database and due to the huge amount of configuration variants it is 
				possible that it &lt;br&gt;might not produce the expected results.&lt;br&gt;
				So backup your database (at least the tables sys_template and tt_content) or do a t3d export of your site 
				&lt;strong&gt;BEFORE&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br&gt;
				you click on any of the "DO_IT" Buttons.</label>
				
			<label index="extmng.useStoragePid">Use "General record storage page": This option configures the handling of news categories in BackEnd forms and on the website (for the CATMENU content element the GRSP can be overridden by "displayCatMenu.catPidList"). By default categories will be displayed only if they are found in the "General record storage page" (AKA "GRSP" or "storagePid"). If you set "useStoragePid" to "0", all categories from the pagetree will be displayed. If "useStoragePid" is set to "1" and there are no tt_news categories in the "GRSP" you won't see any categories in BackEnd forms or on the website. See tt_news manual for more information.</label>						
			<label index="extmng.requireCategories">Require categories: Check if categories are required for every news item. Note that you can require categories also through page TSConfig using "TCEFORM.tt_news.category.config.minitems=1"</label>
			<label index="extmng.writeParseTimesToDevlog">Debug parsetimes: Write parsetimes to devlog (extension "devlog" required).</label>

			<label index="extmng.parsetimeThreshold">Parsetime threshold: Execution time in seconds after which a function is logged to devlog. Default 
			is 0.1 sec = 100ms. Means any function in tt_news which needs more time to be executed will be logged. The execution time indicates the
			severity of the log entry: 0-0.2 sec = 0 (info), 0.2-0.5 sec = 1 (notice), 0.5-1 sec = 2 (warning) and everything above 1 second get severerity
			3 = error.</label>

			<label index="extmng.useInternalCaching">Internal caching: If enabled tt_news caches some processing intensive information (archive period count, 
			category count, categories) in an internal cache.</label>
			
			<label index="extmng.writeCachingInfoToDevlog">Debug caching info: Which information about internal caching should be written to devlog
				 (extension "devlog" required)."disabled": don't write any information about caching to devlog. "cache misses": log only cache misses.
				 "all": log cache misses and cache hits to devlog.</label>
		
			<label index="extmng.cachingMode">Caching Mode: Determines the cache entries lifetime and when the internal cache from tt_news will be cleared. 
				"normal": (default) the cache entries will get the same lifetime as normal pages. The tt_news cache will be cleared 
					when the "clear all caches" button is pressed. 
				"lifetime": will set the livetime of cache entries to the given amount of seconds in	field "cacheLifetime". The cache table is not cleared when "clear all caches" is clicked. 
				"static": means: the lifetime of cache entries is set to zero (= unlimited). TYPO3 does not clear the tt_news cache (useful if you clear the cache with an external script or
				for debugging).</label>
			<label index="extmng.cacheLifetime">Cache lifetime: lifetime in seconds of the internal cache entries (if "cachingMode" is set to "lifetime"). example: 86400 (a day), 604800 (a week)</label>
			<label index="extmng.cachingEngine">Caching engine: where should the cache entries from tt_news be stored. "internal": store cache records directly in the database using internal methods. "cachingFramework" Requires at least TYPO3 4.3: store cache records in the TYPO3 caching framework (in the default configuration tt_news uses the DB backend of the caching framework).</label>
			
			
			
			<label index="extmng.treeOrderBy">Category ordering in BackEnd trees: Here you can configure the the ordering of categories in category trees in BackEnd forms.</label>
			<label index="extmng.prependAtCopy">Prepend at Copy: Here you can disable adding of the text "(copy [#])" to titles of copied records.</label>
			<label index="extmng.label">News Label in List-Module: Defines which field is displayed in the title column in the web/list module.</label>
			<label index="extmng.label_alt">Alternative Label: Defines which field is displayed in the title column in lists if the field is empty, that is configured as label. If no alternative label is defined and the label field is empty the text [No title] will be shown.</label>
			<label index="extmng.label_alt2">Alternative Label 2: see "Alternative label."</label>
			<label index="extmng.label_alt_force">Force alternative label: If this is activated the alternative label will be always shown behind the label.</label>
			<label index="extmng.categoryTreeWidth">Width of the right category field: This field shows the category tree in the tt_news db-record (or in the category db-record). If "categoryTreeWidth" is set to 0 (zero) the default width (=350px) will be taken.</label>
			<label index="extmng.categorySelectedWidth">Width of the left category field: This field shows the selected categories in the tt_news db-record (or parent categories in the category db-record). If "categorySelectedWidth" is set to 0 (zero) the default width (=200px) will be taken.</label>
			<label index="extmng.l10n_mode_prefixLangTitle">Localization mode for text fields: By default, all text fields (text, subheader, imagecaption ...) from a new localized news article will be prepended with "[translate to ...]". If this is not wanted you can disable it here. If "l10n_mode_prefixLangTitle" is disabled the text "(copy [#])" will be added to the titles of this records unless "prependAtCopy" is disabled (see "prependAtCopy").</label>
			<label index="extmng.l10n_mode_imageExclude">Localization mode for images: The image field of a localized news article is excluded by default (images are alwas taken from the record in the default language). If you need localized images (f.e. if the images show texts) you can enable the "image" field in translated news by setting "l10n_mode_imageExclude" to 0.</label>
			<label index="extmng.hideNewLocalizations">Hide new localizations: Here you choose if new localizations of news articles should be hidden or not. By default new localizations are visible. If this is not wanted set "hideNewLocalizations" to 1.</label>
			<label index="extmng.updatermsg">tt_news 3.0.0 comes with a new updater-script which can fix some of the most common problems when you're updating an existing tt_news 2.x installation.</label>
			<label index="extmng.updatermsgHeader">Important!</label>
			<label index="extmng.updatermsgLink">[Click here to open the updater]</label>
			<label index="extmng.updatermsgOption">Updater</label>
			
			
			<label index="tsce.templateFile">Template File: HTML-template which is used to display news (e.g.: "fileadmin/templates/my_news_tmpl.html").</label>
			<label index="tsce.pid_list">Starting Point (pid_list): The PID of the page (or comma separated list pf PIDs) where your news articles are stored. Note that getting the pidList can be very performance intensive if you use a high recursion level (plugin.tt_news.recursive) in a big pagetree. If this is a problem for your site, consider to completely disable the use of pidList in database queries (TS-Setup: plugin.tt_news.dontUsePidList).</label>
			<label index="tsce.singlePid">SinglePid: Page on which single news items should be displayed.</label>
			<label index="tsce.backPid">BackPid: Page where the "back to list" link in single view links to.</label>
			<label index="tsce.archiveTypoLink.parameter">Archive Link parameter: The PID of the page with a LIST element that displays only archived news items. This link appears at the bottom of the LATEST template and it is also used for the links in the AMENU.</label>
			<label index="tsce.allowCaching">Allow Caching: Allow caching of displayed news? If you want your news being indexed by the indexed-search this has to be enabled.</label>
			<label index="tsce.useHRDates">Use human readable dates: This enables the use of the GETvars "year" and "month" for the archive links instead of the non-readable "pS", "pL" and "arc".</label>
			<label index="tsce.useSubCategories">Use subcategories: Enable this if news should also be selected for display if they are a member of a subcategory of the selected category. Works only if categoryMode is 1 (="Show items with selected categories").</label>
			<label index="tsce.showCatRootline">Show category rootline: Enable this to show the category rootline in the SINGLE or LIST view.</label>
			<label index="tsce.useBidirectionalRelations">Use bidirectional relations: If this is enabled the SINGLE view shows the the relations of news in both directions. The relation which points back to the source record will be inserted automatically.</label>
			<label index="tsce.usePagesRelations">Use Pages as related news: If this is enabled the SINGLE view shows also relations to pages.</label>
			<label index="tsce.displaySubCategories">Display subcategories: If this is enabled the subcategories of the categories that are assigned to a news record will also be displayed in news records in the FrontEnd. If displayed categories in a news record are subcategories they will be wrapped with "subCategoryTitleItem_stdWrap" (titles) or "subCategoryImgItem_stdWrap" (images).</label>
			<label index="tsce.showRelatedNewsByCategory">Show related news by category: If this is enbaled the SINGLE view shows a list of news with the same category as the current news record.</label>
			<label index="tsce.useSPidFromCategory">Use singlePid from category: If this is enabled tt_news uses the singlePid from the first assigned category.</label>
			<label index="tsce.useMultiPageSingleView">Use Multipage Single View: Enable this if you want to divide the news SINGLE view to multiple pages.</label>
			<label index="tsce.showTitleAsPrevNextLink">Show news title as next/prev link: Enable this if you want to show the title of the linked news article in next/previous links in SINGLE view. If disabled the language labels for "next" and "previous" will be used instead.</label>
			<label index="tsce.limit">List Limit: max items in LIST template.</label>
			<label index="tsce.latestLimit">Latest Limit: max news items in LATEST template.</label>
			<label index="tsce.recursive">Recursive level: extend "pid_list" by the number of recursive levels.</label>
			<label index="tsce.noIconsInRelatedNews">No icons in related news: Disables the tt_news record icons in related news.</label>
			
			<label index="tsce.displayCatMenu.mode">Category menu mode: This configures how the tt_news category menu (catmenu) is rendered. "tree": use TYPO3 treeview class to build an expandable menu, "ajaxtree": expandable menu with ajax (requires TYPO3 4.2 or higher), "nestedWraps": make a category menu with nested wraps (not expandable)</label>
			<label index="tsce.displayCatMenu.showNewsCountForCategories">Show news count in category menu: If enabled the category menu displays the number of news for 
				each category next to the category title.</label>
			<label index="tsce.displayCatMenu.catmenuIconMode">Category menu icon mode: The tree/ajaxtree mode has some special options for configuring the icons. The option  "catmenuIconMode" configures the behaviour of the icons showing left to the category titles.  "catmenuIconMode" offers the following options:
-1 = display no icons at all, 0 = display the default icon (tt_news_cat.gif), 1 = display image from category record as icon, 2 = display the icon which is configured as  "catmenuIconFile"  (default: EXT:tt_news/res/arrow.gif)</label>		
			<label index="tsce.displayCatMenu.catmenuNoRootIcon">No root icon in category menu: Disables the icon for the "root" item of the tree (the catmenu header) if set.</label>		
			<label index="tsce.catmenuWithArchiveParams">Archive parameters in category menu: If enabled the archive period parameters (pS,pL,arc or day,month,year) will be added to links in category menu.</label>		
			
			<label index="tsce.displayCatMenu.expandable">Category menu expandable: enable the expand/collapse links for the category menu</label>		
			<label index="tsce.displayCatMenu.expandAll">Category menu expand all: show always the completely expanded category menu.</label>	
			<label index="tsce.displayCatMenu.expandFirst">Category menu expand first level: start with the first level expanded.</label>	

			
			<label index="tsce.datetimeDaysToArchive">datetime days to Archive: If this is set, news are automatically considered as "archived", when the date from field "datetime" plus the given number of days is in the past. If "datetimeDaysToArchive" is "0" only the field "archivedate" is relevant for the archive.</label>
			<label index="tsce.enableArchiveDate">Enable archivedate: If this is set, the archivemenu selects news by their "archivedate" - if "enableArchiveDate" is disabled, news in the archivemenu will be selected by the field "datetime".</label>
			<label index="tsce.amenuStart">Archivemenu start: Start date for the archive menu (php strtotime() syntax. e.g.: 1.1.2002, -3 months, -10 years, now)</label>
			<label index="tsce.amenuEnd">Archivemenu end: End date for the archive menu (php strtotime() syntax. e.g.: 1.1.2002, -3 months, -10 years, now, 1 year (value can be in the future))</label>
			
			<label index="tsce.amenuWithCatSelector">Category selection in archive menu: If enabled (default) the archive menu respects the selected category from catmenu. If the amenu content element is configured to show only news from a certain category the selected category from catmenu will overide this setting.</label>
			
			<label index="tsce.archiveMode">Archive menu mode: This configures how the archive menu is divided to periods. "month": show a link for each month, "year": show only years, "quarter": divide each year to quarters. </label>
			
			
			<label index="tsce.catTextMode">Category Text mode: This configures how categories in news records should handled. 
				Posible values are: 0 = don't display, 1 = display but don't link (default), 2 = link to category shortcut, 3 = act as category selector (points to a list view showing only the clicked category).</label>
			<label index="tsce.catImageMode">Category Image mode: same options as catTextMode but for category images.</label>
			<label index="tsce.singleMaxW">single-image max Width: Max width for an image displayed in SINGLE template</label>
			<label index="tsce.singleMaxH">single-image max height: Max height for an image displayed in SINGLE template</label>
			<label index="tsce.latestMaxW">latest-image max width: Max width for an image displayed in LATEST template</label>
			<label index="tsce.latestMaxH">latest-image max height: Max height for an image displayed in LATEST template</label>
			<label index="tsce.listMaxW">list-image max width: Max width for an image displayed in LIST template</label>
			<label index="tsce.listMaxH">list-image max height: Max height for an image displayed in LIST template</label>
			
			<label index="tsce.listImageMode">Resize mode for LIST images: If set to "resize2max" images will be scaled until either width or height reaches the maximum value (aspect ratio is preserved). If set to "crop" images will be cropped to the given size (centered). If set to "resize" images will be resized to the given values, the aspect ratio is not preserved.</label>
			<label index="tsce.latestImageMode">Resize mode for LATEST images: see "listImageMode".</label>
			
			
			
			<label index="tsce.xmlFormat">News-Feed XML-Format: Defines the format of the news feed. Possible values are: "rss091", "rss2" "rdf", "atom1" and "atom03"</label>
			<label index="tsce.xmlTitle">News-Feed XML-Title: The title of your news feed. (required for rss091, rss2, rdf and atom03)</label>
			<label index="tsce.xmlLink">News-Feed XML-Link: The link to your hompage. (required for rss091, rss2, rdf and atom03)</label>
			<label index="tsce.xmlDesc">News-Feed XML-Description: The description of your news feed. (required for rss091, rss2 and rdf. optional for atom03)</label>
			<label index="tsce.xmlLang">News-Feed XML-Language: Your site's language. A list of allowable values for &lt;language&gt; in RSS is available at http://backend.userland.com/stories/storyReader$16 (equired for rss091, optional for rss2, not available for rdf, recommended for atom03)</label>
			<label index="tsce.xmlIcon">News-Feed XML-Icon: Provide an icon for your news feed with preferred size of 16x16 px, can be gif, jpeg or png. (required for rss091, optional for rss2 and rdf, not available for atom03)</label>
			<label index="tsce.xmlLimit">News-Feed XML-Limit: max news items in RSS feeds.</label>
			<label index="tsce.xmlCaching">News-Feed XML-Caching: Allow caching for the RSS feed</label>
			<label index="tsce.rss2_tmplFile">RSS-News rss v2 Template File: XML template for RSS 2.0 feed</label>
			<label index="tsce.rss091_tmplFile">RSS-News rss v0.91 Template File: XML template for RSS 0.91 feed.</label>
			<label index="tsce.rdf_tmplFile">RDF-News RDF Template File: XML template for RDF feed.</label>
			<label index="tsce.atom03_tmplFile">Atom-News Atom v0.3 Template File: XML template for Atom 0.3 feed.</label>
			<label index="tsce.atom1_tmplFile">Atom-News Atom v1.0 Template File: XML template for Atom 1.0 feed.</label>
			
			
			
			
			
			
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="dk" type="array">
			<label index="pi_title">Nyheder</label>
			<label index="pi_plus_wiz_description">Tilføjer nyheder til siden.</label>
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="de" type="array">
			<label index="pi_title">News</label>
			<label index="pi_plus_wiz_description">Vielseitiges News-System für TYPO3</label>
			
			
			<label index="extmng.back">[&lt;- zurück]</label>
			<label index="extmng.lbl_searchOutdatedTempl">Suche nach veralteten TypoScript Templates</label>			
			
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="no" type="array">
			<label index="pi_title">Nyheter</label>
			<label index="pi_plus_wiz_description">Tilføyer nyhetselementer på siden.</label>
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="it" type="array">
			<label index="pi_title">News</label>
			<label index="pi_plus_wiz_description">Aggiungi news alla pagina</label>
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="fr" type="array">
			<label index="pi_title">Actualités</label>
			<label index="pi_plus_wiz_description">Système de gestion des Actualités pour TYPO3</label>
			<label index="cms_layout.mode">Affichage : %s</label>
			<label index="cms_layout.not_configured">Le plugin n'est pas configuré !</label>

			<label index="updater.back">[&lt;- retour]</label>
			<label index="updater.reload">[recharger la page]</label>

			<label index="updater.lbl_searchOutdatedTempl">Recherche des gabarits TS statics dépassés</label>
			<label index="updater.msg_searchOutdatedTempl">Recherche des gabarits TS incluant un des gabarits statics tt_news mais avec une adresse dépassée :</label>
			<label index="updater.foundMsg_searchOutdatedTempl"> ###COUNT### enregistrement(s) de gabarit trouvé(s).</label>
			<label index="updater.question_searchOutdatedTempl">Mettre à jour ces enregistrements ?</label>

			<label index="updater.lbl_searchNonExistingHtml">Recherche de template HTML inexistant</label>
			<label index="updater.msg_searchNonExistingHtml">Recherche de contenus tt_news avec des templates HTML définis dans les flexforms n'existant pas sur le serveur :</label>
			<label index="updater.foundMsg_searchNonExistingHtml">###COUNT### enregistrement(s) de contenu trouvé(s).</label>
			<label index="updater.question_searchNonExistingHtml">Nettoyer ces paramètres ?</label>


			<label index="updater.lbl_searchMovedPidlist">Recherche de "Startingpoint" ("pages") dans les flexforms</label>
			<label index="updater.msg_searchMovedPidlist">Recherche de contenu tt_news avec une valeur pour le champ "Startingpoint" (ce champ a été déplacé dans un autre onglet):</label>
			<label index="updater.foundMsg_searchMovedPidlist"> ###COUNT### enregistrement(s) de contenu trouvé(s).</label>
			<label index="updater.question_searchMovedPidlist">Conserver ces paramètres ?</label>

			<label index="updater.lbl_searchMovedRecursive">Recherche de "récursif" dans les flexforms</label>
			<label index="updater.msg_searchMovedRecursive">Recherche de contenu tt_news avec une valeur pour le champ "récursif" (ce champ a été déplacé dans un autre onglet):</label>
			<label index="updater.foundMsg_searchMovedRecursive">###COUNT### enregistrement(s) de contenu trouvé(s).</label>
			<label index="updater.question_searchMovedRecursive">Conserver ces paramètres ?</label>


			<label index="updater.lbl_searchMovedNoPageBrowser">Recherche de "noPageBrowser" dans les flexforms</label>
			<label index="updater.msg_searchMovedNoPageBrowser">Recherche de contenu tt_news avec une valeur pour le champ "noPageBrowser" (ce champ a été déplacé dans un autre onglet):</label>
			<label index="updater.foundMsg_searchMovedNoPageBrowser">###COUNT### enregistrement(s) de contenu trouvé(s).</label>
			<label index="updater.question_searchMovedNoPageBrowser">Conserver ces paramètres ?</label>

			<label index="updater.lbl_searchMovedListLimit">Recherche de "listLimit" dans les flexforms</label>
			<label index="updater.msg_searchMovedListLimit">Recherche de contenu tt_news avec une valeur pour le champ "listLimit" (ce champ a été déplacé dans un autre onglet):</label>
			<label index="updater.foundMsg_searchMovedListLimit">###COUNT### enregistrement(s) de contenu trouvé(s).</label>
			<label index="updater.question_searchMovedListLimit">Conserver ces paramètres ?</label>

			<label index="updater.warningHeader">Important ! à lire svp !</label>
			<label index="updater.nothingtodo">Rien à faire</label>
			<label index="updater.warningMsg">l'updater manipule votre base de données et, étant donné la grande quantité de configuration possible, il est possible que cela &lt;br&gt;
                                ne produise pas le résultat attendu.&lt;br&gt;
				Donc, sauvegardez votre base de données (notamment les tables sys_template et tt_content) ou faites un export t3d de votre site
				&lt;strong&gt;AVANT&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br&gt;
				de cliquer sur un bouton de validation.</label>

			<label index="extmng.useStoragePid">Utiliser la page générale de stockage des enregistrements : Cette option configure le traitement des catégories d'actualité dans les formulaires Back Office et sur le site (pour le contenu "CATMENU" le GRSP peut être surchargé avec "displayCatMenu.catPidList"). Par défaut, les catégories seront affichées uniquement si elles sont trouvées dans cette page de stockage (AKA "GRSP" ou "storagePid"). Si vous paramétrez "useStoragePid" à "0", toutes les catégories de l'arborescence seront affichées. Si "useStoragePid" est paramétré à "1" et s'il n'y a pas de catégorie dans le "GRSP" vous ne verrez aucune catégorie, ni dans les formulaires Back Office, ni sur le site. Voir le manuel tt_news pour plus d'information.</label>
			<label index="extmng.requireCategories">Catégories obligatoires : Sélectionner cette option si les catégories sont obligatoires pour toutes les actualités. Notez que vous pouvez forcer l'utilisation des catégories sur des pages données du site via le paramétrage de page TSConfig en utilisant "TCEFORM.tt_news.category.config.minitems=1"</label>
			<label index="extmng.writeParseTimesToDevlog">Debug parsetimes: Ecrit les "parsetimes" dans le devlog (extension "devlog" nécessaire).</label>

			<label index="extmng.parsetimeThreshold"> Seuil parsetime : Délai d'exécution en seconde après lequel une fonction est loguée dans le devlog. Par défaut
			 0.1 sec = 100ms. Cela signifie que toute fonction de tt_news nécessitant plus de temps pour être exécutée sera loguée. Le délai d'exécution indique la
			sévérité du log: 0-0.2 sec = 0 (information), 0.2-0.5 sec = 1 (observation), 0.5-1 sec = 2 (alerte) et tout log au dessus d'1 seconde prend la sévérité
			3 = erreur.</label>

			<label index="extmng.useInternalCaching">Caching interne : Si activé, tt_news met en cache des information de processing (nombre de période d'archivage,
			nombre de catégories, les catégories) dans un cache interne.</label>

			<label index="extmng.writeCachingInfoToDevlog">Debuguer les information de cache: Quelles informations du cache interne doivent être écrites dans le devlog
				 (extension "devlog" nécessaire)."désactivé": n'écrit aucune information du cache dans le devlog. "cache misses": logue unquement les actions ratées.
				 "all": logue tous les caches dans le devlog.</label>

			<label index="extmng.cachingMode">Mode de Caching: Détermine la durée de vie des entrées du cache et quand le cache interne de tt_news doit être vidé.
				"normal": (valeur par défaut) les entrées du cache ont la même durée de vie que les pages normales. Le cache de tt_news sera vidé
                                        quand le bouton "vider tous les caches" sera cliqué.
				"lifetime": paramètre la durée de vie des entrées du cache avec le nombre de secondes du champ "cacheLifetime". La table des caches n'est pas vidée quand le bouton "vider tous les caches" est cliqué.
				"static": signifie que la durée de vie des entrées du cache est égale à 0 (= illimitée). TYPO3 ne vide pas les caches de tt_news (utile lorsque vous videz les caches avec un script externe ou
                                pour debugger).</label>
			<label index="extmng.cacheLifetime">Durée de vie du cache: durée de vie en secondes des entrées du cache interne (si le "cachingMode" est paramétré à "lifetime"). exemple: 86400 (1 jour), 604800 (une semaine)</label>
			<label index="extmng.cachingEngine">Moteur de caching: où les entrées du cache de tt_news seront stockées ? "internal": stocke les enregistrement du cache directement dans la base de données en utilisant les méthodes internes. "cachingFramework" Nécessite TYPO3 4.3: stocke les enregistrements du cache dans le nouveau framework de caching TYPO3 (par défaut, tt_news utilise la base de données back office du framework de caching).</label>



			<label index="extmng.treeOrderBy">Tri des catégories dans les arborescences du Back Office : Ici vous pouvez configurer la clé de tri des arborescences de catégories dans les formulaires back office.</label>
			<label index="extmng.prependAtCopy">Préfixer lors de la copie : Ici vous pouvez désactiver l'ajout de texte"(copy [#])" dans les titres des enregistrements copiés.</label>
			<label index="extmng.label">Libellé des actualités en mode liste : Définit quel champ sera affiché dans la colonne titre dans le module web/liste.</label>
			<label index="extmng.label_alt">Libellé alternatif : Définit quel champ sera affiché dans la colonne titre en mode liste si le libellé par défaut est vide. Si aucun libellé alternatif n'est défini et que le libellé est vide, le texte [sans titre] sera affiché.</label>
			<label index="extmng.label_alt2">Libellé alternatif 2: Libellé alternatif."</label>
			<label index="extmng.label_alt_force">Forcer les libellés alternatifs : Si cette option est activée les libellés alternatifs seront toujours affichés derrière le libellé par défaut.</label>
			<label index="extmng.categoryTreeWidth">Largeur de la zone de droite du champ catégorie : Cette zone affiche l'arborescence des catégories dans les formulaires back office des enregistrements d'actualité (ou des enregistrements de catégories). Si cette option est paramétrée à 0  (zero) la largeur par défaut (=350px) sera utilisée.</label>
			<label index="extmng.categorySelectedWidth">Largeur de la zone de gauche du champ catégorie : Cette zone affiche les catégories sélectionnées dans le champ catégories des formulaires back office des enregistrements d'actualités (ou des enregistrements de catégories). Si cette option est paramétrée à 0  (zero) la largeur par défaut (=200px) sera utilisée.</label>
			<label index="extmng.l10n_mode_prefixLangTitle">Mode de traduction pour les champs texte : Par défaut, tous les champs texte (texte, titre, étiquette d'image...) dans une nouvelle traduction d'actualité seront préfixés avec "[translate to ...]". Si ce n'est pas souhaité, vous pouvez désactiver cela ici. Si "l10n_mode_prefixLangTitle" est désactivé, le texte "(copy [#])" sera ajouté aux titres des enregistrements même si "prependAtCopy" est désactivé (voir "prependAtCopy").</label>
			<label index="extmng.l10n_mode_imageExclude">Mode de traduction pour les images : Le champ image d'une actualité traduite est exclu par défaut (les images sont toujours récupérées à partir de l'enregistrement de la langue par défaut). Si vous souhaitez traduire les images (ex: si une images contient des textes) vous pouvez activer le champ image dans les actualités traduites en paramétrant "l10n_mode_imageExclude" à 0.</label>
			<label index="extmng.hideNewLocalizations">Cacher les nouvelles traductions : Ici vous pouvez choisir si les nouvelles traductions d'actualité doivent être cachées par défaut ou pas. Par défaut les nouvelles traductions sont visibles. Si ce n'est pas souhaité, paramétrer "hideNewLocalizations" à 1.</label>
			<label index="extmng.updatermsg">tt_news 3.0.0 contient un nouvel  Updater qui permet de résoudre la majeur partie des problèmes courants lorsque vous mettez à jour une installation tt_news 2.x existante.</label>
			<label index="extmng.updatermsgHeader">Important !</label>
			<label index="extmng.updatermsgLink">[Cliquez ici pour ouvrir l'Updater]</label>

			<label index="tsce.templateFile">Fichier template : template HTML utilisé pour afficher les actualités(ex : "fileadmin/templates/my_news_tmpl.html").</label>
			<label index="tsce.pid_list">Page de stockage (pid_list): le PID de la page (ou liste de PIDs séparée par des virgules) où les actualités sont stockées. Notez que l'utilisation de la pidList peut être très lourd en termes de performances si vous utilisez un niveau de récursion élevé (plugin.tt_news.recursive) sur une arborescence de site importante. Si cela pose un problème pour votre site, désactivez totalement l'utilisation de la pidList dans les requêtes de BDD (TS-Setup: plugin.tt_news.dontUsePidList).</label>
			<label index="tsce.singlePid">Page de vue single : PID de la page sur laquelle les vues détaillées des actualités seront affichées.</label>
			<label index="tsce.backPid">Page de retour : PID de la page vers laquelle mène le lien "retour" des vues single.</label>
			<label index="tsce.archiveTypoLink.parameter">Page des archives : PID de la page contenant la liste des actualités archivées. Le lien vers cette page est affiché en bas des vues "LATEST" et est également utilisé dans les liens du "AMENU".</label>
			<label index="tsce.allowCaching">Autoriser le caching: Si vous souhaitez que vos actualités soient indexées par indexed search, ceci doit être activé.</label>
			<label index="tsce.useHRDates">Utiliser des dates lisibles : Ceci active l'utilisation de paramètres GET lisibles tels que "year" et "month" pour les liens vers les archives à la place des paramètres "pS", "pL" et "arc".</label>
			<label index="tsce.useSubCategories">Utiliser les sous-catégories: Séléctionnez cette option pour sélectionner les actualités faisant partie de sous catégories de la catégorie sélectionnée. Ne fonctionne que si categoryMode = 1 (="Afficher les enregistrements appartenant aux catégories sélectionnées").</label>
			<label index="tsce.showCatRootline">Afficher la rootline des catégories : Activez cette option pour afficher la rootline des catégories dans les vues SINGLE ou LIST.</label>
			<label index="tsce.useBidirectionalRelations">Utiliser les relations bidirectionnelles : Si cette option est activée, la vue SINGLE affiche les relations des actualités dans les deux directions. Les relations qui vont vers l'enregistrement source seront insérées automatiquement.</label>
			<label index="tsce.usePagesRelations">Utiliser les pages en tant qu'actualité liée: Si cette option est activée, la vue SINGLE affiche également les relations vers les pages.</label>
			<label index="tsce.displaySubCategories">Afficher les sous catégories : Si cette option est activée, les sous catégories des catégories assignées à une actualité seront également affichées dans les enregistrements en Front Office. Si les catégories affichées dans une actualité sont des sous catégories, elles seront wrappées avec "subCategoryTitleItem_stdWrap" (titres) ou "subCategoryImgItem_stdWrap" (images).</label>
			<label index="tsce.showRelatedNewsByCategory">Afficher les actualités liées par catégorie : Si cette option est activée la vue SINGLE affiche la liste des actualités appartenant à la même catégorie que l'actualité affichée.</label>
			<label index="tsce.useSPidFromCategory">Utiliser la page Single à partir de la catégorie : Si cette option est activée, tt_news utilise la page de vue single définie pour la première catégorie assignée.</label>
			<label index="tsce.useMultiPageSingleView">Utiliser des vues single multiples : Activez cette option si vous voulez utiliser plusieurs pages de vue single.</label>
			<label index="tsce.showTitleAsPrevNextLink">Afficher les titres des actualités à la place des liens précédent/suivant : Activez cette option si vous voulez afficher le titre de l'actualité dans les liens précédent / suivant dans les vues SINGLE. Si cette option est désactivée, les textes (traduits selon la langue) "précédent" et "suivant" seront affichés.</label>
			<label index="tsce.limit">Limite de la vue LIST: Nombre maximum d'enregistrements dans la vue LIST.</label>
			<label index="tsce.latestLimit">Limite de la vue LATEST: Nombre maximum d'enregistrements dans la vue LATEST.</label>
			<label index="tsce.recursive">Profondeur (niveau de récursion) : Etend la fonction "pid_list" avec un niveau de récursion.</label>
			<label index="tsce.noIconsInRelatedNews">Pas d'icône dans les actualités liées: Désactive les icônes dans les actualités liées.</label>

			<label index="tsce.displayCatMenu.mode">Mode du menu des catégories: Ceci configure la façon dont le menu des catégories de tt_news est affiché (catmenu). "tree": utilise la class TYPO3 "treeview" pour construire un menu arborescent, "ajaxtree": le menu est dynamique avec ajax (nécessite TYPO3 4.2 ou supérieur), "nestedWraps": créé un menu avec des wraps imbriqués (non dynamique)</label>
			<label index="tsce.displayCatMenu.showNewsCountForCategories">Afficher le nombre d'actualités dans le menu des catégories : Si cette option est activée, le menu des catégories affiche le nombre d'actualités pour chaque catégorie à côté du titre de la catégorie.</label>
			<label index="tsce.displayCatMenu.catmenuIconMode">Mode d'affichage des icônes du menu des catégories : les modes tree/ajaxtree ont des options spéciales pour configurer les icônes. L'option  "catmenuIconMode" configure le comportement des icônes affichés à gauche des titres des catégories. "catmenuIconMode" offre les options suivantes :
-1 = n'affiche pas d'icône du tout, 0 = affiche l'icône par défaut (tt_news_cat.gif), 1 = affiche l'image de l'enregistrement de catégorie en tant qu'icône, 2 = affiche l'icône qui est configurée dans  "catmenuIconFile"  (default: EXT:tt_news/res/arrow.gif)</label>
			<label index="tsce.displayCatMenu.catmenuNoRootIcon">Pas d'icône à la racine du menu des catégories : Désactive l'icône pour l'item situé à la racine de l'arborescence du menu des catégories (le "catmenu header") si cette option est sélectionnée.</label>
			<label index="tsce.catmenuWithArchiveParams">Paramètres d'archivage dans le menu des catégories : Si cette option est sélectionnée, les paramètres d'archivage (pS,pL,arc or day,month,year) seront ajoutés dans les liens du menu des caégories.</label>

			<label index="tsce.displayCatMenu.expandable">Menu des catégories extensible : active les liens plier/déplier pour le menu des catégories.</label>
			<label index="tsce.displayCatMenu.expandAll">Menu des catégories - tout déplier : montre toujours le menu des catégories complètement déplié.</label>
			<label index="tsce.displayCatMenu.expandFirst">Menu des catégories - déplier le premier niveau : affiche le menu des catégories en dépliant le premier niveau.</label>


			<label index="tsce.datetimeDaysToArchive">Délai d'archivage en jours: Si cette option est sélectionnée, les actualités sont automatiquement considérées comme archivées lorsque la date du champ "datetime" + le nombre de jours donnés est dépassée. Si cette option est à "0" seul le champ "archivedate" est pris en compte pour l'archivage.</label>
			<label index="tsce.enableArchiveDate">Activer la date d'archivage : Si cette option est sélectionnée, le menu des archives sélectionne les actualités par leur date d'archivage "archivedate" - si "enableArchiveDate" est désactivé, les actualités du menu des archives seront sélectionnées par le champ date "datetime".</label>
			<label index="tsce.amenuStart">Début du menu des archives: Date de début pour le menu des archives (Syntaxe php strtotime() ex: 1.1.2002, -3 months, -10 years, now)</label>
			<label index="tsce.amenuEnd">Fin du menu des archives: Date de fin pour le menu des archives (Syntaxe php strtotime() ex: 1.1.2002, -3 months, -10 years, now, 1 year (la valeur peut être dans le futur))</label>

			<label index="tsce.amenuWithCatSelector">Sélection des catégories dans le menu des archives : Si cette option est sélectionnée (par defaut) le menu des archives respecte la catégorie sélectionnée à partir du "catmenu". Si le contenu "AMENU" est configuré pour afficher seulement les actualités d'une certaine catégorie, la catégorie sélectionnée à partir du "catmenu" surchargera ce paramètre.</label>

			<label index="tsce.archiveMode">Mode d'affichage du menu des archives : Ceci configure la façon dont le menu des archives est divisé en périodes. "month": affiche un lien par mois, "year": affiche uniquement les années, "quarter": divise chaque année en trimestre. </label>


			<label index="tsce.catTextMode">Mode d'affichage du texte des catégories : Ceci configure la gestion des catégories dans les enregistrements des actualités.
				Les valeurs possibles sont : 0 = ne pas afficher, 1 = afficher mais sans lien (par defaut), 2 = lien de raccourci vers la catégorie, 3 = agit comme un selecteur de catégorie (pointe vers une vue liste affichant uniquement la catégorie cliquée).</label>
			<label index="tsce.catImageMode">Mode d'affichage des images des catégories: mêmes options que "catTextMode" mais pour les images des catégories.</label>
			<label index="tsce.singleMaxW">Largeur maximum de la "single-image" : Largeur maximum de l'image affichée dans la vue SINGLE</label>
			<label index="tsce.singleMaxH">Hauteur maximum de la "single-image": Hauteur maximum de l'image affichée dans la vue SINGLE</label>
			<label index="tsce.latestMaxW">Largeur maximum de la "latest-image" : Largeur maximum de l'image affichée dans la vue LATEST</label>
			<label index="tsce.latestMaxH">Hauteur maximum de la "latest-image" : Hauteur maximum de l'image affichée dans la vue LATEST</label>
			<label index="tsce.listMaxW">Largeur maximum de la "list-image" : Largeur maximum de l'image affichée dans la vue LIST</label>
			<label index="tsce.listMaxH">Hauteur maximum de la "list-image" : Hauteur maximum de l'image affichée dans la vue LIST</label>

			<label index="tsce.listImageMode">Mode de redimensionnement pour les images en mode LIST : Si cette option est paramétrée à "resize2max" les images seront redimensionnées jusqu'à ce que la largeur ou la hauteur atteigne la valeur maximum (les proportions sont préservées). Si cette option est paramétrée à "crop" les images seront rognées et centrées afin d'atteindre les dimensions. Si cette option est paramétrée à "resize" les images seront redimensionnées sans respecter les proportions.</label>
			<label index="tsce.latestImageMode">Mode de redimensionnement pour les images en mode LATEST : voir "listImageMode".</label>



			<label index="tsce.xmlFormat">Format du flux XML des actualités : Définie le format XML du flux des actualités. Les valeurs possibles sont: "rss091", "rss2" "rdf", "atom1" et "atom03"</label>
			<label index="tsce.xmlTitle">Titre du flux XML des actualités : Définie le titre du flux XML des actualités. (obligatoire pour les formats rss091, rss2, rdf et atom03)</label>
			<label index="tsce.xmlLink">Lien du flux XML des actualités : Définie le lien vers la homepage du flux XML des actualités. (obligatoire pour les formats rss091, rss2, rdf et atom03)</label>
			<label index="tsce.xmlDesc">Description du flux XML des actualités : Définie la description du flux XML des actualités. (obligatoire pour les formats rss091, rss2 and rdf. optionnel pour le format atom03)</label>
			<label index="tsce.xmlLang">Langue du flux XML des actualités : La langue du site. Une liste des valeurs acceptées dans les flux XML est disponible à l'adresse http://backend.userland.com/stories/storyReader$16 (obligatoire pour les formats rss091, optionnel pour le format rss2, non disponible pour le format rdf, recommandé pour le format atom03)</label>
			<label index="tsce.xmlIcon">Icône du flux XML des actualités : Produit un icône pour le flux XML des actualités avec une taille de 16x16 px, peut être un gif, un jpeg ou un png. (obligatoire pour les formats rss091, optionnel pour le format rss2 et rdf, non disponible pour le format atom03)</label>
			<label index="tsce.xmlLimit">Limite du flux XML des actualités: nombre maximum d'actualités pour le flux XML.</label>
			<label index="tsce.xmlCaching">Caching du flux XML des actualités: Autorise le caching pour le flux XML.</label>
			<label index="tsce.rss2_tmplFile">Fichier template Actualités RSS v2: Template XML pour le flux RSS 2.0.</label>
			<label index="tsce.rss091_tmplFile">Fichier template Actualités RSS v0.91: Template XML pour le flux RSS 0.91.</label>
			<label index="tsce.rdf_tmplFile">Fichier template Actualités RDF: Template XML pour le flux RDF.</label>
			<label index="tsce.atom03_tmplFile">Fichier template Actualités Atom v0.3: Template XML pour le flux Atom 0.3.</label>
			<label index="tsce.atom1_tmplFile">Fichier template Actualités Atom v1.0: Template XML pour le flux Atom 1.0.</label>		
			
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="es" type="array">
			<label index="pi_title">Noticias</label>
			<label index="pi_plus_wiz_description">Añade noticias a la página.</label>
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="nl" type="array">
			<label index="pi_title">Nieuws</label>
			<label index="pi_plus_wiz_description">Voegt nieuws aan de pagina toe.</label>
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="cz" type="array">
			<label index="pi_title">Zprávy</label>
			<label index="pi_plus_wiz_description">Vloží zprávy na stranu.</label>
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="pl" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="si" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="fi" type="array">
			<label index="pi_title">Uutiset</label>
			<label index="pi_plus_wiz_description">Lisää uutiset sivulle</label>
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="tr" type="array">
			<label index="pi_title">Haberler</label>
			<label index="pi_plus_wiz_description">Sayfaya haber ekle</label>
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="se" type="array">
			<label index="pi_title">Nyheter</label>
			<label index="pi_plus_wiz_description">Lägger en nyhetsmodul till sidan.</label>
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="pt" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="ru" type="array">
			<label index="pi_title">Новости</label>
			<label index="pi_plus_wiz_description">Добавляет список новостей на страницу</label>
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="ro" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="ch" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="sk" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="lt" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="is" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="hr" type="array">
			<label index="pi_title">Novosti</label>
			<label index="pi_plus_wiz_description">Dodaje novosti na stranicu</label>
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="hu" type="array">
			<label index="pi_title">Hírek</label>
			<label index="pi_plus_wiz_description">Hírek megjelenítése az oldalon</label>
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="gl" type="array">
			<label index="pi_title">Nutaarsiassat</label>
			<label index="pi_plus_wiz_description">Nutaarsiassat quppernermut ilanngunneqassapput</label>
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="th" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="gr" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="hk" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="eu" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="bg" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="br" type="array">
			<label index="pi_title">Notícias</label>
			<label index="pi_plus_wiz_description">Adiciona notícias à página.</label>
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="et" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="ar" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="he" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="ua" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="lv" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="jp" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="vn" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="ca" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="ba" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="kr" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="eo" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="my" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="hi" type="array">
		</languageKey>
	</data>
	<orig_hash type="array">
		<languageKey index="dk" type="array">
			<label index="pi_title" type="integer">231848472</label>
			<label index="pi_plus_wiz_description" type="integer">69242695</label>
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="de" type="array">
			<label index="pi_title" type="integer">231848472</label>
			<label index="pi_plus_wiz_description" type="integer">69242695</label>
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="no" type="array">
			<label index="pi_title" type="integer">231848472</label>
			<label index="pi_plus_wiz_description" type="integer">69242695</label>
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="it" type="array">
			<label index="pi_title" type="integer">231848472</label>
			<label index="pi_plus_wiz_description" type="integer">69242695</label>
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="fr" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="es" type="array">
			<label index="pi_title" type="integer">231848472</label>
			<label index="pi_plus_wiz_description" type="integer">69242695</label>
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="nl" type="array">
			<label index="pi_title" type="integer">231848472</label>
			<label index="pi_plus_wiz_description" type="integer">69242695</label>
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="cz" type="array">
			<label index="pi_title" type="integer">231848472</label>
			<label index="pi_plus_wiz_description" type="integer">69242695</label>
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="pl" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="si" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="fi" type="array">
			<label index="pi_title" type="integer">231848472</label>
			<label index="pi_plus_wiz_description" type="integer">69242695</label>
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="tr" type="array">
			<label index="pi_title" type="integer">231848472</label>
			<label index="pi_plus_wiz_description" type="integer">69242695</label>
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="se" type="array">
			<label index="pi_title" type="integer">231848472</label>
			<label index="pi_plus_wiz_description" type="integer">69242695</label>
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="pt" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="ru" type="array">
			<label index="pi_title" type="integer">231848472</label>
			<label index="pi_plus_wiz_description" type="integer">69242695</label>
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="ro" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="ch" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="sk" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="lt" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="is" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="hr" type="array">
			<label index="pi_title" type="integer">231848472</label>
			<label index="pi_plus_wiz_description" type="integer">69242695</label>
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="hu" type="array">
			<label index="pi_title" type="integer">231848472</label>
			<label index="pi_plus_wiz_description" type="integer">69242695</label>
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="gl" type="array">
			<label index="pi_title" type="integer">231848472</label>
			<label index="pi_plus_wiz_description" type="integer">69242695</label>
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="th" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="gr" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="hk" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="eu" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="bg" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="br" type="array">
			<label index="pi_title" type="integer">231848472</label>
			<label index="pi_plus_wiz_description" type="integer">69242695</label>
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="et" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="ar" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="he" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="ua" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="lv" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="jp" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="vn" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="ca" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="ba" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="kr" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="eo" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="my" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="hi" type="array">
		</languageKey>
	</orig_hash>
	<orig_text type="array">
		<languageKey index="dk" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="de" type="array">
			<label index="pi_title">News</label>
			<label index="pi_plus_wiz_description">Versatile news system for TYPO3</label>
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="no" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="it" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="fr" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="es" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="nl" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="cz" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="pl" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="si" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="fi" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="tr" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="se" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="pt" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="ru" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="ro" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="ch" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="sk" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="lt" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="is" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="hr" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="hu" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="gl" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="th" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="gr" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="hk" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="eu" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="bg" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="br" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="et" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="ar" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="he" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="ua" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="lv" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="jp" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="vn" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="ca" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="ba" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="kr" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="eo" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="my" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="hi" type="array">
		</languageKey>
	</orig_text>
</T3locallang>